liebermans.net 2017-07-12

# Lieberman's Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Lieberman's. As important as it is to provide you with a wide selection of the finest art, please know we are committed to protecting your privacy.

  * We are committed to protecting our customers' personal information.
  * We only use personal information to process your orders and provide a personalized, rewarding customer experience. 
  * We use the latest technology and best business practices to protect all personal information.
  * We NEVER sell, rent or give away your personal information.
  * By using our site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy.

## **Orders**

We require certain personally identifiable information to process your order: contact information (name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (credit card number and expiration date). We use this information to bill, confirm, and ship your orders. If we cannot process your order, we use the information to contact you. All purchases and credit card transactions sent through Lieberman's are private and secure.

## **How We Use Your Personal Information**

In addition to fulfilling your order, we collect personal information to make our products and services more rewarding and easier to use. We primarily use this information to improve our customers' experience. We may also use your information to contact you for customer satisfaction surveys, account and promotional purposes. 

We only share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as delivering packages, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, fulfilling orders and other similar functions. These partners only have access to the data required to complete the task assigned to them and are committed to upholding our privacy standards. 

Such companies may have access to a limited set of personal information in order to perform their roles, but they may not disclose your information for other purposes.

## **We Do Not Sell, Rent or License Any of Our Customer's Personal Informaion**

We may share aggregate web site usage information with marketing partners and affiliates. This information does not identify individual users and is only used for statistical purposes.

## **Security**

The security of your personal information is critical to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, nor is any method of electronic storage. Therefore, while we strive to use every available resource to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our site, please contact us as indicated below.

## **Opting Out of Newsletters, Special Offers and Product Updates**

From time to time, we may send you newsletters or information on special offers, promotions, or product updates. If you decide you no longer wish to receive these communications, you may stop receiving them by following the opt-out instructions included in each newsletter or email communication, by contacting customer service at (800) 644-1278, or writing to us at the address below.

## **Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information.

"Web beacons", or clear gifs, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar to cookies, are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Web beacons help us manage site content by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personally identifiable information.

## **Links to Other Sites**

This site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

## **Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding the use of our site or our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
  Lieberman's  
  49 Stouts Lane  
  Monmouth Junction, NJ 08852  
  800-418-2166
